dramawall.com 2019-06-25

# Privacy Policy - Drama Wall

This **[privacy policy](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Privacy_policy)** sets out how DramaWall.com uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website. DramaWall.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. DramaWall.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from Nov 11, 2017.

 **What we collect We may ask to collect the following information:**

e-mail address (for use to send you the daily [DramaWall.com](http://www.dramawall.com/) newsletter, which you can unsubscribe from at any time  
Additionally, we collect non-personally identifiable information for aggregation such as, among other things, visitor browser type and screen resolution.

 **Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

 **How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Additionally, DramaWall.com utilizes cookies to show our advertisements to you on various websites on the Internet.

You may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting Google’s [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads).

 **Third Party Vendors**

Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior website visits.  
Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visits to DramaWall.com and/or other sites on the Internet.  
You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads).

Third parties may use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect or receive information from your website and elsewhere on the internet and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads.

Links to other websites Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

 **Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

 **Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**Amazon Services LLC Associates Program**

[www.dramawall.com](http://www.dramawall.com/) is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to [www.dramawall.com](http://www.dramawall.com/) (amazon.com, or endless.com, MYHABIT.com, SmallParts.com, or AmazonWireless.com).

 **Newsletter**

When signing up to our newsletter you agree with the terms in this Privacy Policy. We shall email you weekly a list of the latest articles that were posted on the site. You agree also to us sending you periodic emails about how to learn the thai language and how to live in Thailand. These emails may have links to other websites other than www.dramawall.com. If you click a link from one of our newsletters and are directed to another site other than www.dramawall.com you agree to the privacy policy of that email as it may differ to that of www.dramawall.com. We will not sell, rent or trade your email to another website. You may choose at any time to be removed from the newsletter either by using the Unsubscribe link in the newsletter email. We use MailChimp as our email newsletter provider and have shared your email address with them. If you wish to see their privacy policy and terms then please use this link [here](http://mailchimp.com/about/mcsv/ "Mail Chimp Terms").
